Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/le-nguyen-thi-truc-thuy-925978140 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Automotive

Scrum

Software Testing

Certifications

Professional Scrum Master™ I (PSM I)

Photoshop

Microsoft Certified: Azure Data Fundamentals

ISTQB Foundation

Introduction To Data Science For Business

Le Nguyen Thi Truc Thuy

Business Analyst at FPT Software

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Now, I am a Business Analyst, Quality Control, and UX/UI designer based in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. I have prior experience in several industries relating to gamification, commerce, and retail. My passions are traveling, watching youtube, and living healthy.

Experience

FPT Software Software Tester October 2024 - Present (6 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

FPT Software

4 years

Business Analyst
March 2019 - August 2022 (3 years 6 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Software Tester September 2018 - February 2019 (6 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

A&C AUDITING AND CONSULTING COMPANY LIMITED

Auditor

January 2018 - March 2018 (3 months)

Thanh Pho Nha Trang, Khanh Hoa, Vietnam

Education

University Of Economics Ho Chi Minh City
Bachelor's degree, Business Accounting · (September 2014 - July 2018)

Tamkang University

Master's degree, Data Science · (September 2022 - July 2024)

Page 1 of 2